Finding Aid for Ann Arbor (Mich.) Government Publications, circa 1956-2001
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
Ann Arbor (Mich.) government publications circa 1956-2001
Ann Arbor (Mich.)
3 linear feet
0575 Cc 2
Scattered publications of various city offices.
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
The Ann Arbor (Mich.) Publications were received as individual items or as part of various accessions.
The record group is open without restriction.
Miscellaneous publications of various Ann Arbor city government offices and departments. The publications are organized by the name of the creating office.
Subjects:
Ann Arbor (Mich.)--Politics and government.
Contributors:
Ann Arbor (Mich.). Anti-Substance Abuse Task Force.; Ann Arbor (Mich.). Central Area Development Task Force.; Ann Arbor (Mich.). Circulation Plan Special Committee.; Ann Arbor (Mich.). Citizen Advisory Committee.; Ann Arbor (Mich.). Citizen's Commission on Children and Youth.; Ann Arbor (Mich.). Citizens' Committee on Community Development.; Ann Arbor (Mich.). City Administrator's Office.; Ann Arbor (Mich.). Common Council.; Ann Arbor (Mich.). Community Development Dept.; Ann Arbor (Mich.). Community Planning and Management.; Ann Arbor (Mich.). Community Renewal Program.; Ann Arbor (Mich.). Dept. of Parks and Recreation.; Ann Arbor Downtown Development Authority.; Ann Arbor (Mich.). Engineering Dept.; Ann Arbor Historic District Commission (Mich.); Ann Arbor (Mich.). Housing Commission.; Ann Arbor (Mich.). Human Relations Commission.; Ann Arbor (Mich.). Individual Historic Properties District Study Committee.; Ann Arbor (Mich.). Mayor's Blue Ribbon Committee on Fair Rental Practices.; Ann Arbor (Mich.). Model Cities Program.; Ann Arbor (Mich.). Office of the City Controller.; Ann Arbor (Mich.). Office of Community Services.; Ann Arbor (Mich.). Personnel/Human Rights Dept.; Ann Arbor (Mich.). Police Dept.; Ann Arbor (Mich.). Solid Waste Dept.
- Anti-Substance Abuse Task Force
  - Final report on city of Ann Arbor study on substance abuse, 1990 (Box 1)
- Central Area Development Task Force
  (Central Area Plan Citizen Task Force)
  - Ann Arbor's central area: a vision and agenda for the future, 1987 (Box 1)
  - Central Area Plan bulletin, October 1991 (Box 1)
- Circulation Plan Special Committee
  - Meeting notes, July 1, 1975-July 19, 1976 (Box 1)
- Citizen Advisory Committee
  - Draft summary statement for Citizen Advisory Committee, 1975 (Box 1)
- Citizens' Commission on Children and Youth
  - Annual report, 1963/64 (Box 1)
- Citizens' Committee on Community Development
  - Finalized listing of program and project area allocations, 1974 (Box 1)
  - Table showing cross reference between Citizens' Committee on Community Development program areas and activities and needs, long range objectives, and short range objectives, 1975 (Box 1)
- City Administrator's Office, 3 folders
  - Annual report, 1967/68, 1976/77, 1987/88, 1988/99, 1989/90, 1990/91, 1991/92, 1992/93 (Box 1)
  - Budget, executive summary, 1989/90 (Box 1)
  - City of Ann Arbor income tax feasibility study, July 1993 (Box 1)
  - Directory of city services, 1991-1992, 1995, 1997, 2001 (Box 1)
  - Diversity '92 Diversity in the workplace: a report on affirmative action by the city of Ann Arbor, October 1992 (Box 1)
- City Council
  - Rules of the Council including pertinent charter provisions, 1956 (Box 2)
- Community Development, Office of
  - Community development newsletter February 1977, April 1977, January 1978, February 1978, April 1978 (Box 2)
  - Your housing rehabilitation program March 1977 (Box 2)
- Community Planning and Management, 4 folders
  - 1974 C.P.M. survey on citizen attitudes, March 1975 (Box 2)
  - Ann Arbor bicycle path study, prepared by Haldon L. Smith. July 1972 (Box 2)
  - The Ann Arbor planning process: an organizational analysis. [circa 1972 (Box 2)
  - The formulation of city-wide goals and objectives, 1976 (Box 2)
  - Downtown housing opportunity study: the feasibility of renovating upper story space, by H. Pamela Goodman. January 1975. (Box 2)
  - Financing Ann Arbor's city government, March 1974 (Box 2)
  - Financing Ann Arbor's city government, September 1974 (Box 2)
  - Housing stock data base. [1972?], 1973 (Box 2)
  - Management planning and scheduling 1973 (Box 2)
  - Municipal cost/revenue impact analysis for Pittsfield Valley Farms. August 1976. (Box 2)
  - Organization charts for the city of Ann Arbor, 1973, 1975, 1980 (Box 2)
  - Preparing Ann Arbor's budget: fiscal 1974/1975. June 1974 (Box 2)
- Community Renewal Program
  - Ann Arbor community renewal program, 1971 (Box 2)
- Community Services, Office of
  - Report to the Superintendent of Schools and the Ann Arbor Board of Education: new and planned housing developments within the Ann Arbor School district, 1979 (Box 2)
- Controller's Office
  - Comprehensive annual financial report city of Ann Arbor, county of Washtenaw, State of Michigan, fiscal year ended June 30, 1988 (Box 2)
- Downtown Development Authority
  - Ann Arbor downtown plan, Ann Arbor, Michigan, July 1988 (Box 2)
  - Development plan and tax increment financing plan for the Ann Arbor downtown development district, October 26, 1982 (Box 2)
- Energy Advisory Board
  - Proposed energy work plan, 1982 (Box 2)
- Engineering Department/Division
  - Broadway/Wall TSM project proposal, 1981 (Box 3)
  - Proposed street improvements for Packard Road Carpenter to Shadford... 1967 (Box 3)
- Historic District Commission
  - Historical data on the building at 1037 Jones Drive (formerly 1037 Mill Street)... September 22, 1972 (Box 3)
- Housing Commission
  - Fifth report of the Citizens' Committee on Tenant Relations, February 27, 1970 (Box 3)
- Human Relations Commission
  - The population distribution of racial minorities in Ann Arbor, Michigan, 1950-1960 (Box 3)
  - Program prospectus, 1968 (Box 3)
- Individual Historic Properties District Study Committee
  - 500 North Main Street--The Kellogg-Warden House, final report, 1993 (Box 3)
  - Appendix A: Documentation of individual historic properties... 1994 (Box 3)
- Mayor's Blue Ribbon Committee on Fair Rental Practices
  - [letter to Hon. Albert H. Wheeler, Mayor], 1977 (Box 3)
- Model Cities Program
  - [Comprehensive first year action program], draft, 1970 (Box 3)
  - First year action plan, 1970 (Box 3)
  - Mid-planning statement, 1969 (Box 3)
- Parks and Recreation, Dept. of
  - Annual report
    - 1958/59 (Box 3)
    - 1961/62 (Box 3)
  - Report proposing parkland acquisition policy and guidelines (2 versions): one is a summary report for public distribution (Box 3)
- Personnel Human Rights Department
  - Happenings of by & for city employees of Ann Arbor, January /February 1984-March /April 1984 November /December 1984 March /April 1985 (Box 3)
- Police Department, 2 folders
  - Annual report, 1956-1957, 1982, 1986 (Box 3)
  - C.O.P. community oriented policing: become a part of the answer 1992 (Box 3)
  - Fiscal report, 1980/81 (Box 3)
  - Monthly report, June 1994-July 1994, September 1994-February 1995, April 1995-May 1995, August 1995-January 1996, April 1996-May 1996, September 1996, February 1997-March 1997, May 1997, October 1997-December 1997, June 1998 (Box 3)
- Solid Waste, Department of
  - Disposing of commercial trash: 1990 survey of Ann Arbor commercial establishments, final report, 1990 (Box 3)
- Transportation Division
  - Areawide topics plan for the Ann Arbor-Ypsilanti Urban area, 1972 (Box 3)
  - Old West Side residential parking permit report, March 1993 (Box 3)
- Miscellaneous
  - Audit report, 1958 (Box 3)
  - Comprehensive circulation study prospectus for the city of Ann Arbor 1973 (Box 3)
  - Comprehensive housing affordability strategy, draft for comment, 1991 (Box 3)
  - Municipal civil defense and disaster control plan, undated (Box 3)
  - Project and status report, 1969 (Box 3)